Ring in the rivalry.
The Mistle-Tones is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Paul Hoen.
Holly, blessed with an amazing singing voice, is all set to audition for the newly vacated spot in
a legendary local Christmas group which was founded by her late mother years ago.
Shocked and upset when the slot goes to the barely talented best friend of the group's
leader, Marci, Holly sets out to create her own musical group, The Mistle-Tones.
After challenging their rivals to a sing-off on Christmas Eve, Holly finds herself on a journey to the
real meaning of Christmas with some new friends and a new love thrown in for good measure.
Holly, played by Tia Mowry.
Marci, played by Tori Spelling.
Holly's Dad, played by Reginald VelJohnson.
AJ, played by Andy Gala.
Nick, played by Jonathan Patrick Moore.
Grace, played by Tammy Townsend.
The Mistle-Tones is a made-for-TV movie musical that premiered on
December 9, 2012 as part of ABC Family's 25 Days of Christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.